<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Be Prepared</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Help">ABOUT
        \nWelcome! Be Prepared is a reminder app. It allows you to create a list of places you
        frequently visit called destinations. For each destination you can create a list of items.
        This is a list of items that you do not want to forget to bring with you when you head out
        to that place. There are four different modes to help you accomplish this. There is a manual
        mode which allows you to bring up a checklist of items for a destination. The other three
        modes work automatically after you set them up and start them. They remind you to bring up
        the checklist and make sure you have everything before heading out. The different modes
        are explained in more detail below.

        \n\nEDIT LISTS
        \nClicking on the Edit Lists button takes you to the list of destinations. Click the Add
        Destination button to enter a new destination. The only restriction on naming is it cannot
        contain a new line character. You may enter as many destinations as you want. After creating
        a destination it will appear in a list below the Add Destination button. Click on a
        destination and you can delete it or edit the list of items for that destination. If you
        choose to edit it then you will be brought to an edit items list which works the same as the
        edit destinations list.

        \n\nMANUAL MODE
        \nThis is the simplest mode. This button will bring you to your list of destinations if you
        have created it already. Clicking on a destination will bring you to a checklist for that
        particular destination.

        \n\nTIMER MODE
        \nThis mode is the most useful if you know ahead of time when you will be heading out. Just
        use the timer wheel to set the correct hour, minute, and AM/PM then hit the SET button. You
        can then exit the app and it will notify you with your default notification tone and
        vibration. A notification icon will be displayed in the status bar. Clicking on it will
        bring you to the notification screen and ask if you are heading out. Selecting yes will
        take you to the list of destinations where clicking on one will bring you to the checklist
        of items for that destination. If you set a different time before the original timer goes
        off it will update to the new time you entered and the old timer will not go off.

        \n\nWIFI MODE
        \nThis mode works by detecting wifi networks. You will set up a home network and once you set
        it to start the app will notify you as soon as you leave the area of that network. To use
        this mode first make sure to have wifi enabled. If wifi is enabled then you will see a list
        of networks in range once you click on the wifi mode button. The list is scrollable if it
        is longer than the screen. Select the network you would like to use and click on it. A
        dialog box will open that lets you set that network as your home network. Once it is set
        it will display at the top of the screen that it is set as home. Then you can hit the green
        start button. You can then navigate away from the app. It will continue scanning until you
        open wifi mode again and hit the stop button. As long as it is scanning the app will notify
        you in the same way as the timer mode once you leave the area of that network. The scan will
        stop after the notification and will have to be started again when you wish to use it.

        \n\nGPS MODE
        \nThis mode works with GPS and boundary detection. You will set up a bounded area around your
        home and upon leaving this are the app will notify you in the same way the wifi mode does
        when leaving the network area. To use this mode first make sure you have GPS enabled. When
        you open this mode you will see a start button and four direction buttons. For each of the
        directions, move the device to the edge of your home area in that direction. For example,
        move to the northern most wall in your house then hit the north button. It will open a
        dialog that lets you scan the location or delete a previously saved location. The scan will
        scan for about three seconds and save the most accurate result the device receives. Each
        time you scan the most accurate result will be stored so feel free to scan as many time as
        you wish. Just make sure to not move the device while you scan. Three meters is the most
        accurate result in my experience. After all four directions are set you can hit the green
        start button to start a scan. It will continue scanning until you open GPS mode again and
        hit the stop button. As long as it is scanning the app will notify you in the same way as
        the timer mode once you leave the bounded area. The scan will stop after the notification
        and will have to be started again when you wish to use it. Because of the inaccuracy of
        measurements the notification will often go off after moving well beyond the boundary that
        you set up. Wifi mode is usually the better option in terms of battery life and reliability
        unless there are no networks in range.
     </string>
    <string name="wifi_list"> network 1\n network 2\n network 3</string>
    <string name="north">North:</string>
    <string name="east">East:</string>
    <string name="south">South:</string>
    <string name="west">West:</string>
    <string name="track">track</string>
    <string name="stop">stop</string>
    <string name="text_color">#0000FF</string>
    <string name="text_size">28sp</string>
</resources>
